

# KIM NGUYEN

FULL-STACK WED DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

I am a full-stack web developer, I have built several personal projects with M.E.R.N stack and I am learning some new technologies everyday to expand my expertise. I love using number to measure my processes, with 2 hours of practice a day, it will be 730 hours a year.

# **SKILLS**

#### **Coding Languages**

Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL, MongoDB, SaSS.

## Frameworks/Systems

React JS, Bootstrap, NodeJS, JQuery, OAuth, PassportJS, Git, Github, Git Bash.

## **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**

#### **Centria University of Applies Sciences**

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology

- Attended from Feb. 2017 to Dec. 2020.
- Taking up specialization courses in software engineering to broaden skillset.
- Taking up electives in cyber security

### **Certificated Web Bootcamps**

- GGULIVRR (Generic Game for Ubiquitous Learning in Interactive Virtual and Real Realities) in University of Łódz.
- Kokkola Smart City digital workshop in Centria University of Applied Sciences.
- DUDE Show Your Digi! digital workshop in Centria University of Applied Sciences

## WORKING EXPERIENCES

#### Front-end Developer

Centria Summer Workshop | May 2019 to August 2019

- Designed and created mobiles application with Ionic framework.
- Developed and managed development processes with Wrike and Jira Software
- Create and testing application in a short time with Agile development methodology.

#### **Full-stack Web Developer**

Centria R&D Dep | June 2020 to December 2020

 Developed web application with ReactJS, ExpressJS, NodeJS, and MongoDB, OAuth, PassportJS.

## HOW TO REACH ME

Cell: +358 465 472 595

Email: kimnguyen.dev@gmail.com

Address: Vidnäsinkatu 02 - a202, 67100

Kokkola

Linkedin: @kim-nguyen-xuong

Github: @nguyenxuongkim2103